<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" media="screen" href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~d/styles/rss2full.xsl"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" media="screen" href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~d/styles/itemcontent.css"?><rss xmlns:blogChannel="http://backend.userland.com/blogChannelModule" xmlns:feedburner="http://rssnamespace.org/feedburner/ext/1.0" version="2.0">

<channel>
<title>Daily Kos</title>
<link>http://www.dailykos.com</link>
<description>State of the Nation</description>
<copyright>Copyright 2005 - Steal what you want</copyright>
<pubDate>Mon,  Dec 14:27:13 8 GMT</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Mon,  Dec 14:27:13 8 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<managingEditor>Daily Kos &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</managingEditor>
<webMaster>Daily Kos &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</webMaster>

<atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/dailykos/index" type="application/rss+xml" /><feedburner:browserFriendly>This is an XML content feed. It is intended to be viewed in a newsreader or syndicated to another site, subject to copyright and fair use.</feedburner:browserFriendly><item>
<title>Your Abbreviated Pundit Round-up</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/Z4wBu45GZ4w/670581</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Monday, and the pundits are rested! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2008/12/08/opinion/08kristol.html"&gt;William Kristol&lt;/a&gt;: &amp;nbsp;Let's get real. The public likes big government, and anyone running as a small-government conservative is kidding themselves. Of course, we're a center-right country [except when it comes to, you know, reality.] &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;I can&amp;rsquo;t help but admire some of my fellow conservatives&amp;rsquo; loyalty to the small-government cause. It reminds me of the nobility of Tennyson&amp;rsquo;s Light Brigade, as it charges into battle: "Theirs but to do and die." Maybe it would be better, though, first to reason why. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Come to think of it, what about conservatism is successful?&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://online.wsj.com/article/SB122869836736986933.html"&gt;Nicole Galinas&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;President-elect Barack Obama has announced the "single largest new investment in our national infrastructure since the creation of the federal highway system in the 1950s." Getting this once-in-a-generation opportunity right doesn't involve reinventing the wheel, but rather leadership and competence at all levels of government. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Writing in the WSJ, I forgot to add that this desire for competence shows we're a center-right country (if we don't keep repeating it, people will forget.)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2008/12/07/AR2008120701975.html"&gt;Emil W. Henry Jr.&lt;/a&gt;: Big government? This conservative is for it. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Many conservatives are uneasy with such talk -- clinging to the notion that government investment or oversight is anathema to Reagan orthodoxy and other core conservative beliefs. They fear the creation of another permanent bureaucracy, foresee a strain on the budget at a time of extreme economic distress and argue that such spending is an ineffective economic stimulus. These are all legitimate worries, but they miss the bigger point: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt; We're up the creek without a paddle, our ideas have failed, and the public knows it. But don't despair. After all, we're a center-right country.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.newsweek.com/id/172567"&gt;Fareed Zakaria&lt;/a&gt;: It's all about Pakistan, and they'd better get their act together.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2008/12/08/opinion/08cohen.html"&gt;Roger Cohen&lt;/a&gt;: Well, these days Paris smells better than Havana, but what's it all mean? Heck if I know.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2008/12/07/AR2008120701925.html"&gt;P. Michael Conn and James V. Parker&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt; The Foundation for Biomedical Research, which tracks attempts to intimidate researchers, has found that a handful of sporadic actions 10 years ago has ballooned to more than a hundred annually. Most involve nonviolent harassment, but a growing number have been violent. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;And while we wait for details, here's what the public thinks (as of 12/3) about the auto bail-out from &lt;a href="http://blogs.abcnews.com/thenumbers/2008/12/big-three-bailo.html"&gt;Gary Langer&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/c78cQ0LeWO7f-HveeBzJDutv-eU/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/c78cQ0LeWO7f-HveeBzJDutv-eU/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=E2rgAYEG"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/Z4wBu45GZ4w" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>DemFromCT &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>Your Abbreviated Pundit Round-up</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">670581</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 12:25:50 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/8/7312/95696/649/670581</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>Open Thread and Diary Rescue</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/M5uLUGOStQ0/670507</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Tonight's Rescue Rangers are HansScholl, jlms qkw, dadanation, Got a Grip and srkp23, with claude as editor.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Sixty seven years ago this date the US Navy base at Pearl Harbor was devasted in a surprise attack that shaped my childhood, and my generation, even though I would not be born for 3 1/2 more years. The assassination of President Kennedy shaped my emerging adulthood, and the end of my life, now approaching, has been shaped unexpectedly by 9/11/2001 in ways that are only now becoming clear. It is necessary to remember things, events, emotions; it is also necessary to grow past them while remembering. I ask that you read and recommend Shocko's thoughtful and evocative diary. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Rescued Diaries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drawing upon his own personal experiences and recollections, &lt;strong&gt;Shocko from Seattle&lt;/strong&gt;'s &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/10120/0508/898/670316"&gt;Some thoughts on the drug war&lt;/a&gt; is a provocative and worthwhile read. (dadanation) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;Seeing one decent man's desire to help others leads &lt;strong&gt;smileycreek&lt;/strong&gt; to wonder &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/131333/350/877/670361"&gt;What Would Wes Do?&lt;/a&gt; (Got a Grip)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;shadow light5&lt;/strong&gt; describes the pitiful situation in Darfur, and the infamous major players, in &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/3725/04445"&gt;Sudan - Darfur's World and Genocide&lt;/a&gt;. (jlms qkw) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;two roads&lt;/strong&gt; takes us back to the mysterious lights that appeared in the sky starting on December 3, 1948 in &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/221536/159/94/668093"&gt;Saturday Night Uforia: Great (Green) Balls o' Fire! - Part 1&lt;/a&gt;. A phenomenal read and a treasure-trove of amazing links! (dadanation) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;shirah&lt;/strong&gt;informs us about the Congressional Research Office and their new report in &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/91448/2035"&gt;New From CRS: Healthcare and taxes in the new administration&lt;/a&gt;. (jlms qkw) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;oceanstar17&lt;/strong&gt; continues a state by state series on political trends in &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/173448/993/42/670171"&gt;Future Trends: Nevada&lt;/a&gt;. (HansScholl)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ardyess&lt;/strong&gt; finds praise for an independent minded Alabama state Supreme Court Justice in a surprising place in &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/213217/095/306/669891"&gt;A brief moment of sanity from Focus on the Family?&lt;/a&gt; (HansScholl)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;In &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/11715/7872/586/662508"&gt;Klamath River Dams To Flood Oregon Legislature&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;bob zimway&lt;/strong&gt; explains why this is going to be a very controversial environmental issue in not just 2009 but for many years after that. (dadanation) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Avenging Angel&lt;/strong&gt; examines the sad truth of &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/135430/777/863/670375"&gt;The Growing Canadian Sacrifice in Afghanistan&lt;/a&gt;. (Got a Grip)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;jotter&lt;/strong&gt; has &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/113637/737"&gt;High Impact Diaries: December 6, 2008&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/12321/2468/891/670339"&gt;Week's High Impact Diaries: November 29 - December 5&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eddie C&lt;/strong&gt; has tonight's &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/215958/473/703/668501"&gt;Top Comments 12-07-2008 - 12-08-1990 Edition&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This is an Open Thread. Play nice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/R7r1oeFyJ7hMWvg8wzlPsTsNhBA/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/R7r1oeFyJ7hMWvg8wzlPsTsNhBA/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=cyLxjVPP"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/M5uLUGOStQ0" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>Diary Rescue &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>open thread</category>
<category>diary rescue</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">670507</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 04:13:43 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/221050/852/707/670507</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>Keith O. Interviews "Prop 8 - The Musical" Stars</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/WiG3BEFOmMg/669994</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Keith O. spends an enjoyable 9 minutes with &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marc_Shaiman"&gt;Mark Shaiman&lt;/a&gt;, the brilliant creative mind behind "Prop 8 - The Musical," and two of its co-stars, &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jack_Black"&gt;Jack Black&lt;/a&gt; (who knew Jesus was Black!?) and &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_C._Reilly"&gt;John C. Reilly&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe width="425" scrolling="no" src="http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/22425001/vp/28077550#28077550" height="339"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This is protest, 21st century style...and it couldn't be more fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/ripCqmk3ZuPD2u7U9PNcFRhGAkc/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/ripCqmk3ZuPD2u7U9PNcFRhGAkc/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=DSesNjBm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/WiG3BEFOmMg" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>Jed L &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>Proposition 8</category>
<category>Keith Olbermann</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">669994</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 03:11:18 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/221118/359/219/669994</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>OH-15: Kilroy (D) wins!!!</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/6r8LmuRzrQo/670467</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;If you're like me, you woke up this morning feeling pretty lousy. Paul Carmouche hasn't lost yet in LA-04, but the odds are against him winning with provisional and absentee ballots, or with a recount. It's possible he could pull this out - he's only 356 votes back - but it will be tough.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;With Dollar Bill Jefferson having lost (good) to a Republican (bad), that's a double sting. I'm glad Jefferson is gone, but the Republicans are going to have a field day with this (having apparently won the first three elections of the Obama Era, including one in a D+28 district). There were extenuating circumstances and they almost lost an election in LA-04 they should have won, but that won't stop them from having their fun.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;On the (very) bright side, the votes have finally been counted in OH-15, and you can say hello to your newest Congresswoman, Democrat &lt;a href="http://blog.dispatch.com/dailybriefing/2008/12/kilroy_wins.shtml"&gt;Mary Jo Kilroy&lt;/a&gt;. She has won, and there isn't going to be a recount:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now it's official: Mary Jo Kilroy will be going to Washington as the first Democrat to represent any part of Franklin County in Congress in a generation.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Final vote tallies released this evening by the Franklin County Board of Elections show that Kilroy defeated Republican state Sen. Steve Stivers by 2,311 votes, outside of the 0.5 percent margin to trigger a recount.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Kilroy, a Franklin County commissioner, picked up a lopsided majority of provisional ballots counted by the Franklin County Board of Elections over the weekend after a court ruling Friday afternoon. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Congratulations to everyone involved in the Kilroy race - the candidate, her campaign, the DCCC, Franklin County Democrats, the OSU Dems, volunteers, contributors, everyone.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;This is a lovely win, especially after the tremendous disappointment of last night.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Republican Steve "Steve" Stivers has conceded, which oughta leave him plenty of time for &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/6/17/151447/997"&gt;window shopping&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/DI6NAuesGuy4ic28PJ6ngvTdEq8/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/DI6NAuesGuy4ic28PJ6ngvTdEq8/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=9vwjtkGg"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/6r8LmuRzrQo" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>brownsox &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>OH-15</category>
<category>Ohio</category>
<category>House</category>
<category>2008</category>
<category>Mary Jo Kilroy</category>
<category>Steve Stivers</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">670467</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2008 00:53:37 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/193559/633/763/670467</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>Sebelius for Senate?</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/Ite7jVLlJ_w/670356</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Kathleen Sebelius spent a good deal of time on the road this year, campaigning for Barack Obama. It is well-known she was a finalist in the &lt;a href="http://archives.chicagotribune.com/2008/aug/21/news/chi-ap-ia-sebelius-obama"&gt;VP sweepstakes&lt;/a&gt; and there has been a &lt;a href="http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/28076701/"&gt;great deal of speculation&lt;/a&gt; she would be named to a cabinet position - possibly as the Secretary of Labor, Energy, or Education.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Yesterday, Kathleen Sebelius put an end to that speculation by abruptly announcing she was &lt;a href="http://www.kansascity.com/842/story/925301.html"&gt;withdrawing her name from consideration&lt;/a&gt; for any cabinet position, saying she wanted to finish her term and focus on the economic challenges in Kansas.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;What does this mean for Sebelius? She is term-limited and cannot run for governor again in 2010. Sam Brownback has announced he does not intend to run for re-election to the Senate in 2010 and is making it known he is interested in &lt;a href="http://www2.ljworld.com/news/2008/sep/04/brownback_considering_gubernatorial_run_2010/"&gt;running for governor&lt;/a&gt; (bleh). Nonetheless, this leaves an opportunity for Sebelius to run for his open seat. She is well-liked throughout the state and has the best chance for a Democratic Senate victory since the 1930's......the last time Kansans elected a Democrat to represent them in the Senate. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Congressman Emanuel Cleaver has also suggested she would be an "awesome" &lt;a href="http://www.kansascity.com/115/story/925678-p2.html"&gt;head of the DNC&lt;/a&gt;. She probably would be a good fit for the DNC, but the prospect of her running for Senate is much more exciting.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Other Kansas Democrats - like Dennis Moore - have been hedging on whether they might run for Brownback's seat, seemingly waiting to see what Sebelius does with the Obama administration. Now that she has formally withdrawn herself for consideration of a cabinet position, let's hope it is a signal she does intend to run for senate in 2010. She has the best opportunity to win in generations and it sure would be nice to finally see some Jayhawk blue representation in Washington.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/t9JgqfZ26sboRYenotr7S1FrK78/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/t9JgqfZ26sboRYenotr7S1FrK78/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=5EFdZKj8"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/Ite7jVLlJ_w" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>Scout Finch &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>Kathleen Sebelius</category>
<category>Sam Brownback</category>
<category>Dennis Moore</category>
<category>Emmanuel Cleaver</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">670356</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 22:08:27 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/12568/4180/874/670356</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>Midday Open Thread</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/dhkXv9eCkCU/670341</link>
<description>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; It's official.....David Gregory has been named as the &lt;a href="http://www.sfgate.com/cgi-bin/article.cgi?f=/n/a/2008/12/07/entertainment/e070949S10.DTL&amp;amp;tsp=1"&gt;new host of Meet the Press.&lt;/a&gt; He takes the reins next Sunday.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt; The McClatchy Company continues to feel the economic pinch. There is new speculation McClatchy is trying to &lt;a href="http://www.reuters.com/article/businessNews/idUSTRE4B50NH20081206?feedType=RSS&amp;amp;feedName=businessNews"&gt;sell the Miami Herald.&lt;/a&gt; Real estate ad sales in Florida have been decreasing, hurting the paper's already thin margins.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;After 28 years in a coma, Sonny von Bulow &lt;a href="http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20081206/ap_on_re_us/obit_von_bulow"&gt;passed away Saturday&lt;/a&gt; at the age of 76. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt; Thieves in Paris made off with &lt;a href="http://www.google.com/hostednews/afp/article/ALeqM5iwWQbQvtK5Ol63bVQ-L6BZvwwcCA"&gt;$100 million in jewels&lt;/a&gt; after robbing the Harry Winston boutique just off the Champs-Elysees avenue.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt; The Cuban government is &lt;a href="http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20081205/ap_on_re_la_am_ca/cb_cuba_bloggers"&gt;cracking down on Cuban bloggers.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Yoani Sanchez and husband and fellow blogger Reynaldo Escobar were summoned separately Wednesday to a police station near their apartment in Havana's Vedado district and reprimanded, Escobar said in a telephone interview. &lt;br /&gt;Authorities told the couple they could not travel to the western province of Pinar del Rio for a two-day blogger's workshop scheduled to begin Friday night. &lt;br /&gt;"We aren't attending the inauguration of the workshop, which has not been suspended. We've just changed the dynamic of how we are meeting," said Escobar, without elaborating. &lt;br /&gt;An account of the reprimand appears on Sanchez's blog, "Generacion Y." The site was blocked to Internet users on the island Friday. &lt;br /&gt;Sanchez wrote that police told her, "We want to warn you that you have transgressed all the limits of tolerance with your closeness and contact with elements of the counterrevolution." &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;li&gt;From &lt;a href="http://thinkprogress.org/2008/12/07/rove-haters/"&gt;Think Progress&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Karl Rove is reportedly one of the key architects overseeing the &amp;#8220;Bush legacy project,&amp;#8221; predicting that the President will be remembered as a &amp;#8220;far-sighted leader.&amp;#8221; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also reserved for between the covers of Rove&amp;#8217;s book is his checklist of the &amp;#8220;great many of the political actors in this town (who) never accepted him as a legitimate president.&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;ve got behind-the-scenes episodes that are going to show how unreceiving they were of this man as president of the United States,&amp;#8221; Rove said, adding: &amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m going to name names and show examples.&amp;#8221; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;Oh brother. The only way Bush will be remembered as far-sighted is when people talk about his reading glasses. And if Rove is going to name all those names, it's going to be a big-ass book. - &lt;em&gt;BarbinMD&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;li&gt;CNN &lt;a href="http://www.politico.com/news/stories/1208/16283.html"&gt;plans to try&lt;/a&gt; and steal the thunder from NBC and David Gregory this week by announcing that John King will replace Wolf Blitzer as host of "Late Edition." - &lt;em&gt;BarbinMD&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;Paul Carmouche (LA-04) isn't &lt;a href="http://www.talkingpointsmemo.com/archives/247101.php"&gt;conceding&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;... the margin was only 356 votes out of more than 90k cast. And Carmouche is not conceding.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Follow up shows there's a pretty good reason why. The current totals do not include provisional ballots (which often heavily favor Democrats) or absentee ballots (which in the past often favored Republicans but now can cut either way). They'll both be counted on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Carmouche is also signaling he'll likely ask for a recount. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;  - &lt;em&gt;BarbinMD&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/8gvxLSPXaYUEcVEGnRbIgP6sSic/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/8gvxLSPXaYUEcVEGnRbIgP6sSic/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=uMBtJUqg"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/dhkXv9eCkCU" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>Scout Finch &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>open thread</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">670341</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 21:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/12201/3562/889/670341</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>Gates and the National Defense Strategy</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/EgQJ6G8rVmg/670370</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;For what have been described as reasons of "continuity," President-elect Obama has chosen to retain Robert Gates as his Secretary of Defense, at least for the short term. &amp;nbsp;It's of no small interest, then, to see what Secretary Gates has post-Obama-nod to say about his vision for the future of the military. &amp;nbsp;Just how much continuity are we in for? &amp;nbsp;As it turns out, Gates&amp;rsquo; &lt;a href="http://www.foreignaffairs.org/20090101faessay88103/robert-m-gates/how-to-reprogram-the-pentagon.html"&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; in the January/February issue of &lt;em&gt;Foreign Affairs&lt;/em&gt;, posted Dec. 5, &amp;nbsp;claims basically to be a summary and affirmation of the 23-page Department of Defense &lt;em&gt;2008 National Defense Strategy&lt;/em&gt;, published in June. &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="http://www.defenselink.mil/news/2008%20national%20defense%20strategy.pdf"&gt;(PDF)&lt;/a&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;It is not instantly a good sign for prospects of change that Gates thought this was a good idea. &amp;nbsp;But, to be fair, I went and read the 2008 NDS; maybe it wouldn't be so bad. &amp;nbsp;As it happens, my initial reaction to the NDS was a total non-sequitur: I thought it was hilarious. &amp;nbsp;I felt kind of bad for Gates because he probably had to read it, too. &amp;nbsp;But there is a lesson buried in the NDS's joke-value; so I would like to dwell on that for a moment, before moving on to more obviously substantive matters.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The NDS &amp;#8211; not Gates' article but the original document &amp;#8211; is a study in scrupulous vacuity; it is intended to fill up a lot of white space with sentences bearing zero semantic content. &amp;nbsp;As a matter of democratic openness this makes the NDS very suspect &amp;#8211; it is more of a diversion from than a look into the actual thinking of the Pentagon. &amp;nbsp;As a matter of reading pleasure, it makes the NDS downright hilarious. &amp;nbsp;Nowhere outside a Freshman comp class have so many words struggled so heroically to say so little. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;From the text &lt;a href="http://www.defenselink.mil/news/2008%20national%20defense%20strategy.pdf"&gt;(PDF)&lt;/a&gt; of the 2008 National Defense Strategy of the United States:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;First &amp;#8211;class technology means investing in the right kinds of technology at the right time.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Deterrence is key to preventing attack and enhancing security.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Technology and equipment are tools of the Total Force, and we must give our people what they need, and the best resources, to get the job done.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;We must maintain the capabilities required to defeat state adversaries, including those armed with nuclear weapons.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;We will further develop and enhance our own capabilities. &amp;nbsp;We should continue to develop innovative capabilities, concepts, and organizations. &amp;nbsp;We will continue to rely on adaptive planning, on integration and use of all government assets, and on flexibility and speed.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Missile defenses not only deter an attack, but can defend against such an attack should deterrence fail.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know about you, but I am thrilled to learn that "technology and equipment are tools." &amp;nbsp;On the other hand, I would have thought that "deterrence" is not just key to "preventing attack and enhancing security" but identical with it. &amp;nbsp;Or maybe that&amp;rsquo;s what they meant. &amp;nbsp;As a point of policy, I would like to see President-elect Obama do one of two things: either require future NDSs to be better written for reasons of content and therefore democratic openness about what our National Defense Strategy exactly &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt;, or else stop wasting money putting it together and publishing it.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;However, hiding in the midst of that 23-page semantic vacuum there is actually one sentence of importance. &amp;nbsp;It&amp;rsquo;s the one thing that matters, and the one thing most in need of change under an Obama Administration. &amp;nbsp;Under the bold-faced heading &lt;em&gt;The Strategic Environment&lt;/em&gt; the NDS asserts:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;For the foreseeable future, this environment will be defined by a global struggle against a violent extremist ideology that seeks to overturn the international state system.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is, to put it simply, crazy. &amp;nbsp;The idea that the global military strategic environment will be, is, or ever was &lt;em&gt;defined by&lt;/em&gt; terrorist groups is false. &amp;nbsp;The idea that there is some kind of real military threat in those groups&amp;rsquo; putative goal to "overturn the international state system" is Cheneyistic propoganda at its most extreme. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Everything of any content in the NDS follows from that wacky premise. &amp;nbsp;"Like communism and fascism before it," we are told, the ideology of the guys in the caves demands that they "reject state sovereignty, ignore borders, and attempt to deny self-determination wherever they gain power." &amp;nbsp;That the number of square miles across the globe over which the guys in the caves have &lt;em&gt;actual&lt;/em&gt; power is, within any reasonable margin-of-error, one, seems not to matter to the U.S. Department of Defense under Bush. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Because of the guys in the caves we must put up with "a tension between the need for security and the requirements of openness in commerce and civil liberties." &amp;nbsp;People in other countries must suffer "a prolonged irregular campaign, a violent struggle for legitimacy and influence over the population." &amp;nbsp;We must engage in an ideologically suspect attempt to "shrink the ungoverned areas of the world" and help "others to police themselves and their regions." &amp;nbsp;We must do this all because of the guys in the caves. &amp;nbsp;They "define" our world.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Do I really need to argue the following point? &amp;nbsp;I hope not: Just because we have become so used to living with this nonsense is no excuse to continue on with it under a more-or-less progressive Democratic administration, no matter how valuable military "continuity" might be.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Enter Secretary Gates and his new article in &lt;em&gt;Foreign Affairs&lt;/em&gt;. &amp;nbsp;By comparison to the writing in the National Defense Strategy, he is Shakespeare (assuming he wrote it rather than merely signed it). &amp;nbsp;Unfortunately, what Gates articulates is just a recapitulation of what he&amp;rsquo;s been saying all year; the same stuff found in the NDS. &amp;nbsp;There seems to be no acknowledgement on his part of an impending new Presidency, at all. &amp;nbsp;The problem with continuity is that apparently you get continuity. &amp;nbsp;Secretary Gates &lt;a href="http://www.foreignaffairs.org/20090101faessay88103-p0/robert-m-gates/a-balanced-strategy.html"&gt;writes&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;What is dubbed the war on terror is, in grim reality, a prolonged, worldwide irregular campaign -- a struggle between the forces of violent extremism and those of moderation. Direct military force will continue to play a role in the long-term effort against terrorists and other extremists. But over the long term, the United States cannot kill or capture its way to victory. Where possible, what the military calls kinetic operations should be subordinated to measures aimed at promoting better governance, economic programs that spur development, and efforts to address the grievances among the discontented, from whom the terrorists recruit. It will take the patient accumulation of quiet successes over a long time to discredit and defeat extremist movements and their ideologies.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;And why is "success," however defined, in Iraq and Afghanistan important? &amp;nbsp;Listen for an echo of Rumsfeld:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;The United States' ability to deal with future threats will depend on its performance in current conflicts. To be blunt, to fail -- or to be seen to fail -- in either Iraq or Afghanistan would be a disastrous blow to U.S. credibility, both among friends and allies and among potential adversaries.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Credibility." &amp;nbsp;The reason given when there is no reason. &amp;nbsp;If we are "seen to fail" &amp;#8211; by whom, Gates does not specify, nor why we should care -- our "credibility" will be dealt a "disastrous blow." &amp;nbsp;Not a mild blow. &amp;nbsp;No. &amp;nbsp;A "disastrous" one. &amp;nbsp;Why? &amp;nbsp;What does that even mean?&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;But now we come to the crux of the matter. &amp;nbsp;Beyond Iraq and Afghanistan, out into the great wide world, Gates has a plan for the long war. &amp;nbsp;More special forces, more unmanned aerial planes. &amp;nbsp;Above all, more training of other people&amp;rsquo;s armies to keep their populations in line.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;One of the enduring issues the military struggles with is whether personnel and promotions systems designed to reward the command of American troops will be able to reflect the importance of advising, training, and equipping foreign troops -- something still not considered a career-enhancing path for the best and brightest officers. Another is whether formations and units organized, trained, and equipped to destroy enemies can be adapted well enough and fast enough to dissuade or co-opt them -- or, more significant, to build the capacity of local security forces to do the dissuading and destroying.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Reading this sort of thing, one becomes less and less inclined even to pretend to take the cover-story seriously. &amp;nbsp;This has nothing to do with "terrorists." &amp;nbsp;At the end of his article, Gates comes clean:&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;In world affairs, "what seems to work best," the historian Donald Kagan wrote in his book On the Origins of War and the Preservation of Peace, ". . . is the possession by those states who wish to preserve the peace of the preponderant power and of the will to accept the burdens and responsibilities required to achieve that purpose." I believe the United States' National Defense Strategy provides a balanced approach to meeting those responsibilities and preserving the United States' freedom, prosperity, and security in the years ahead.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thank you. &amp;nbsp;Now, President-elect Obama, could you please explain to Secretary Gates that quoting a neoconservative like &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Donald_Kagan"&gt;Donald Kagan&lt;/a&gt; is no longer allowed; that Kagan&amp;rsquo;s quote is thinly veiled American exceptionalism -- damn near imperialism -- and &lt;em&gt;everyone in the world outside the U.S. knows it&lt;/em&gt;? &amp;nbsp;So much the less acceptable is entertaining Kagan&amp;rsquo;s son &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Kagan"&gt;Robert&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt; (co-founder of The Project for a New American Century, don&amp;rsquo;tcha know) wacky idea, also held by too many others, that invading Iraq counts as "preserv[ing] the peace." &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;While I agree with those saying that the change in staff at the Pentagon under Secretary Gates &amp;#8211; getting rid of the Bush underbelly, as it were -- is a welcome sign, I do not see any concomitant change in vision reflected in Gates' &lt;em&gt;Foreign Affairs&lt;/em&gt; article. &amp;nbsp;The American people deserve to know that elections do have consequences, and that &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; sort of continuity, ideological continuity, will not be tolerated.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;And while you&amp;rsquo;re at it, Mr. President-elect, hire some decent writers for the NDS next time, will ya? &amp;nbsp;That would also be change we can believe in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/nr3IIdlw85i4CU98Bc_SWv02bp0/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/nr3IIdlw85i4CU98Bc_SWv02bp0/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=uURXjYKQ"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/EgQJ6G8rVmg" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>LithiumCola &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>Robert Gates</category>
<category>National Defense Strategy</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">670370</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 18:59:06 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/134729/146/852/670370</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>75 Years Since Repeal Of Prohibition</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/pQMbi4aG50Q/670196</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Seventy-five years ago (&lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/5/105130/936"&gt;December 5, 1933&lt;/a&gt;, to be exact) the United States of America &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Repeal_of_Prohibition"&gt;repealed&lt;/a&gt; its ban on alcoholic beverages.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But even though you won't find a soul alive who thinks the repeal was a bad idea, we continue to live day after day with the disastrous consequences of a drug policy that is as misguided as was prohibition.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On Friday, the &lt;em&gt;Wall Street Journal&lt;/em&gt; published an &lt;a href="http://online.wsj.com/article/SB122843683581681375.html"&gt;op-ed&lt;/a&gt; by Ethan Nadelman, executive director of the &lt;a href="http://www.drugpolicy.org/homepage.cfm"&gt;Drug Policy Alliance&lt;/a&gt;. Nadelman wrote:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Consider the consequences of drug prohibition today: 500,000 people incarcerated in U.S. prisons and jails for nonviolent drug-law violations; 1.8 million drug arrests last year; tens of billions of taxpayer dollars expended annually to fund a drug war that 76% of Americans say has failed; millions now marked for life as former drug felons; many thousands dying each year from drug overdoses that have more to do with prohibitionist policies than the drugs themselves, and tens of thousands more needlessly infected with AIDS and Hepatitis C because those same policies undermine and block responsible public-health policies.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And look abroad. At Afghanistan, where a third or more of the national economy is both beneficiary and victim of the failed global drug prohibition regime. At Mexico, which makes Chicago under Al Capone look like a day in the park. And elsewhere in Latin America, where prohibition-related crime, violence and corruption undermine civil authority and public safety, and mindless drug eradication campaigns wreak environmental havoc.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;All this, and much more, are the consequences not of drugs per se but of prohibitionist policies that have failed for too long and that can never succeed in an open society, given the lessons of history. Perhaps a totalitarian American could do better, but at what cost to our most fundamental values?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Just like you can't find a soul who will say that repeal of prohibition was a mistake, you won't find a soul who will tell you our current drug policy has erased the drug problem.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Yet we continue to treat drug policy as a hypothetical issue, focused on the potential consequences of reform, rather than the disastrous consequences of what we are doing now.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The question isn't just about the pharmacological impacts of drugs. The question is also about the damage our current regulatory regime is inflicting on our society, economy, and criminal justice system. The question is whether we are getting our money's worth from the &lt;a href="http://www.salon.com/opinion/conason/2008/10/20/drug_war/"&gt;$50 billion&lt;/a&gt; we spend each year on the drug war. The question is whether there are better ways to allocate our resources than by focusing the bulk of that money on drugs -- like marijuana -- that are probably &lt;a href="http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/17760130/"&gt;less harmful&lt;/a&gt; than alcohol or tobacco.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But until we collectively -- as citizens -- make it clear to our political leaders that it is acceptable to talk about the consequences of our drug policy, as opposed to a blind focus on nothing but the consequences of drugs, we're never going to make any progress.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If we don't change, we're going to continue having hundreds of brutal murders occuring not just &lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2008/12/05/world/americas/05mexico.html?_r=1&amp;amp;hp"&gt;across the border&lt;/a&gt;, but also right here at home. And we're going to continue to have American citizens addicted to drugs, wasting their futures.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So we need to rethink this drug policy of ours, because it just isn't working. It never has, and until we find the courage to change, it never will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/S0ZTw-FZDKQHDy5b3EdDbNQR3YE/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/S0ZTw-FZDKQHDy5b3EdDbNQR3YE/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=4RxiVyzr"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/pQMbi4aG50Q" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>Jed L &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>Prohibition</category>
<category>drug war</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">670196</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 17:00:04 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/1202/57919/1/670196</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>Rose Aguilar's "Red Highways"</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/KJ-E6XNB7QM/669773</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0979482275?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=daikos-20&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;creativeASIN=0979482275"&gt;Red Highways: A Liberal's Journey Into the Heartland&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;By Rose Aguilar &lt;br /&gt;Polipoint Press, Sausilito, CA &lt;br /&gt;229 pages, $15.95&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;I'm going to admit up front that as a dyed-in-the-wool third generation Democrat raised in one of the reddest parts of my home state, I was initially put off both by the title and a lot of the tone in &lt;em&gt;Red Highways&lt;/em&gt;. The author, Rose Aguilar, is a progressive radio host in that most progressive of American cities, San Francisco, and in her first foray into the publishing world, she decides to undertake a journey (a liberal one, as you can see by the subtitle) into America's "heartland." As if (a) no liberals are there; (b) and she's going to study the conservative heartland natives like they're some freakish tribe just discovered on the banks of the upper Amazon, and she'll interpret their puzzling behavior for us. This tone is scattered throughout the book, with the most irritating tone tic being in the repeated complaints about not being able to find vegan food in places like the Texas panhandle or the backwoods of Mississippi.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Additionally, Aguilar's narrative skills are, to be kind about it, pedestrian. The parts of this book where she accounts scenery, character description or any other sort of travelogue-ish details is flat. If readers come to this book wanting a Bill Bryson or (less comedic choice here) Paul Theroux-style getting-to-know-the-country-and-its-inhabitants, disappointment awaits.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Still, I'm going to recommend this book. Here's why: As a radio personality, Aguilar seems to have a knack for getting all kinds of people to open up and discuss politics and political views. Her questioning skills appear to be stellar, because there are heartening and surprising oral stories that get told here that really are fascinating, backing up anecdotally what a lot of polls are showing -- that people are shifting away from the poles of the traditional conservative/liberal divide and are coming up with hybrids (mostly fiscally conservative, socially liberal).&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Aguilar's journey from San Francisco to the "heartland"--Texas, Oklahoma, Mississippi, Montana, Utah--is undertaken in a beat-up VW van picked up off of Craig's List, with her boyfriend, Ryan, serving as helpmeet along the way. Part of the ongoing interplay between the two is Ryan's quick temper and eagerness to pick political fights and convert folks along the way (he'd make the ideal Kossack in this regard), and Aguilar's more patient (and professional, one assumes) ability to poke a bit and get a tale to unfold from people who are initially reluctant to talk to such a stereotypically "liberal" pair. At times, Aguilar forbids Ryan from entering some venues or approaching certain interviewees; other times, he accompanies her to somewhat riotous effect, such as when he almost starts a fight at a gun show.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;But it's Aguilar's interviewing and genuine interest in the lives of her subjects that makes this book worth reading. Like Studs Terkel, she clearly has a way not only with eliciting stories, but in choosing what to include and exclude in the resultant product. She goes to church and talks to fundamentalist church-goers, even being invited back to their homes. She goes to bars, gun shows, patriotic celebrations. She strikes up conversations in convenience stores, at gas stations, at hometown celebrations. She talks to Democrats who feel stranded and beseiged in a sea of conservative politics, she talks to Republicans who'd die before voting Democratic -- but who profess most of the more progressive party's beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Disdain of Washington, distrust of both political parties (from members of both), loathing of corporations and a feeling from people in these red states that they have more in common with their fellow Americans than the media typically portrays shines through all of Aguilar's encounters. In fact, it would be safe to say that if one theme dominates the book, it's that everyone encountered in the pages, including Aguilar herself and her boyfriend, feel seriously misunderstood. There's a sense that there is, floating above the reality of this country, a media-driven picture of something called "America"-- and then there &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; America itself, jumbled, contradictory, ornery, well-meaning even when misinformed and misguided. A lot of the Republicans the author encounters, for example, are sick to death of their party's emphasis on abortion and homosexuality, but stick with the party out of tradition, while resenting the media assumption that all Republicans feel this way.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Ultimately, this is an uplifting and caring book that gives voice to the unvoiced and that takes most of its power from Aguilar's ability to get out of the way of her subjects and just prod them along. This is no small gift for any author to be able to claim. Despite the objections I made up top here, &lt;em&gt;Red Highways&lt;/em&gt; is a gratifying read, full of life and homespun grit, filled from front to back with people who are trying their best to keep their heads above water, who love this country and who are trying to retain a little bit of dignity in the process of getting by.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/YfPjgAXqEwO00e4tSWUCZaUkBEw/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/YfPjgAXqEwO00e4tSWUCZaUkBEw/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=wSZo0Hj4"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/KJ-E6XNB7QM" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>SusanG &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>Rose Aguilar</category>
<category>Red Highways</category>
<category>book review</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">669773</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 15:00:04 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/1003/69665/440/669773</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>Your Abbreviated Pundit Round-up</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/hYJyH_ecb7o/670285</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Sunday... &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2008/12/07/opinion/07rich.html"&gt;Frank Rich&lt;/a&gt;: Some one had to remind everyone about David Halberstram's The Best and The Brightest, the whiz kids that got us into Vietnam. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;The rest is history that would destroy the presidency of Lyndon Johnson and inflict grave national wounds that only now are healing. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2008/12/07/opinion/07friedman.html"&gt;Tom Friedman&lt;/a&gt;: Forget about the Boomers. It's Gen X that sucks the big one [actually, I mean my contemporaries. Note to myself: I still got it! Whether it's Iraq or politics, no one overgeneralizes like I do.] &amp;nbsp;In any case, Obama is giving America the money... spend it wisely so I can write a book about. Or not. I win an advance either way.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2008/12/07/opinion/07flanagan.htm"&gt;Caitlin Flanagan and Benjamin Schwartz&lt;/a&gt;: On Prop 8 and the African-American vote: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;As anyone who ever had to sit through a lecture on "the paradox of tolerance" can tell you, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to create a vast utopian society forged of many previously disenfranchised groups &amp;mdash; but you don&amp;rsquo;t want to ask too many questions. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Wondering about the generational split? &lt;a href="http://images2.dailykos.com/images/user/426/prop8Age_Race.gif"&gt;The exit polls don't help&lt;/a&gt;, although with everyone other than blacks, there's clearly a generational split. &amp;nbsp;But we forgot to say so. [The full Prop 8 exit poll is &lt;a href="http://www.cnn.com/ELECTION/2008/results/polls/#CAI01p1"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.]&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2008/12/07/opinion/07kristof.html"&gt;Nicholas Kristof&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Americans don&amp;rsquo;t think much about TB, just as we didn&amp;rsquo;t think much of AIDS in the 1980s. But drug-resistant TB is spreading &amp;mdash; half a million cases a year already &amp;mdash; and in a world connected by jet planes and constant flows of migrants and tourists, the risk is that our myopia will catch up with us. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;And yet another reason why health reform needs to include public health, and health research needs proper funding. Are you listening, Tom Daschle and Peter Orszag? &lt;a href="http://www.cdc.gov/fmo/topic/Budget%20Information/index.html"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.nih.gov/news/fundingresearchareas.htm"&gt;NIH&lt;/a&gt; fall under you. More on pandemic preparedness &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/search?offset=0&amp;amp;old_count=30&amp;amp;string=tag%3D%22pandemic+preparedness%22&amp;amp;type=both&amp;amp;sortby=time&amp;amp;search=Search&amp;amp;count=30&amp;amp;wayback=1051200&amp;amp;wayfront=0"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; (there's more than one infectious disease out there.)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2008/12/05/AR2008120502602.html"&gt;David Corn&lt;/a&gt;: My idea of change isn't your idea of change. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;It's no surprise that many progressives are -- depending on whom you ask -- disappointed, irritated or fit to be tied. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;[Note to David Corn: Many progressives are "wait-and-see" and Bowers doesn't speak for everyone any more than we do, but major kudos &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/comments/2008/12/7/72120/2176/50#c50"&gt;for quoting him&lt;/a&gt;.]&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2008/12/05/AR2008120503195.html"&gt;Jim Hoagland&lt;/a&gt;: Well, at least give Obama credit for modernizing the transition. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt; Lengthy presidential transitions rank among the oddest of America's political traditions. In the 21st century, they are also among the most dangerous. The fast start that President-elect Barack Obama is engineering for his economic and foreign policy teams must become a model for his successors. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;a href="http://bostonherald.com/news/opinion/op_ed/view/2008_12_06_Infighting_in_the_making:_President-elect_s_compromised/"&gt;Dick Morris&lt;/a&gt;: I know it's almost Christmas, but if McCain listens to me, he can still win. Oh, and speaking of Christmas, did you know Hillary is the anti-Christ? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/0ImBhxlK21hzb4nhQmQyqt4ubu8/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/0ImBhxlK21hzb4nhQmQyqt4ubu8/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=nWNRC830"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/hYJyH_ecb7o" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>DemFromCT &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>Your Abbreviated Pundit Round-up</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">670285</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 13:05:43 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/72120/2176/929/670285</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>Sunday Talk - Natural Born Thriller</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/XxHqql1Fe8w/665292</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img vspace="5" width="150" hspace="10" align="right" src="http://img147.imageshack.us/img147/8650/turbinefc8.jpg" /&gt;With the Supreme Court widely expected to keep his &lt;a href="http://img247.imageshack.us/img247/4918/colmkbtwluu9.gif"&gt;secret&lt;/a&gt;, Barack Hussein Obama looks to be well on his way to becoming the 44th President of the United States on January 20th.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;But Inauguration Day can't come soon enough for &lt;a href="http://news.yahoo.com/s/ap/20081205/ap_on_go_pr_wh/obama_sidelines"&gt;some people&lt;/a&gt;... they want Obama to start being President now, arguing that the current President is missing in action.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;You know who else was missing in action?&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hint:&lt;/strong&gt; It's not &lt;a href="http://rahmfacts.com/"&gt;Rahm Emanuel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Check under the fold for the answer and other assorted goodies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/j7-jAXq-V-rLO3595bM-UmMvXq0/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/j7-jAXq-V-rLO3595bM-UmMvXq0/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=IBl1uKrL"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/XxHqql1Fe8w" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>SundayTalk &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>Sunday Talk</category>
<category>Recommended</category>
<category>Front Paged</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">665292</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 06:00:56 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/7/1056/25052/861/665292</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>Open Thread and Diary Rescue</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/VkpTfy0HeSE/670244</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This evening's Rescue Rangers are mem from somerville, vcmvo2, srkp23, HansScholl, sunspark says, and joyful, with watercarrier4diogenes at the wheel of the Editmobile&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;The Rangers have sifted and sorted through 229 diaries to bring you these 15 great examples of the excellent writing and breadth of subjects that Teh Orange has become known for.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;In an extensive and copiously sourced review, &lt;strong&gt;Unenergy&lt;/strong&gt; examines a slew of water-based alternative energy strategies: &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/5/75043/5934/615/669590"&gt;A school of electric fish. 20 new wave power ideas.&lt;/a&gt; (mem from somerville) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;In our "post-racial" America, &lt;strong&gt;NLinStPaul&lt;/strong&gt; relates the tale of a man of color who was nearly sentenced to life in prison because of &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/13043/9534/96/670101"&gt;Two Words&lt;/a&gt;. (sunspark says)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;A disheartening and dramatic snapshot of just one small area during &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/5/163630/577/391/669814"&gt;Five days in the Bush Recession&lt;/a&gt; is assembled by &lt;strong&gt;devtob&lt;/strong&gt;. (mem from somerville) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;As huge banks get bailouts, do you think they pay it all forward? (Don't be silly!) &lt;strong&gt;LaKathie&lt;/strong&gt; reports on what's happening as &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/143529/221/65/670132"&gt;200 laid-off factory workers occupy factory, demand owed compensation&lt;/a&gt;. Of course, it somehow all traces back to those big banks... (sunspark says)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tally&lt;/strong&gt; thinks about &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/72959/0705"&gt;Rebranding the FL Dem Party in 2010&lt;/a&gt;. (srkp23)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;As President-elect Obama's new Secretary of HEW requests more information about America's health care crisis, &lt;strong&gt;Kuparuk&lt;/strong&gt; lets him know in &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/124919/160/99/670098"&gt;For Mr. Daschle: My health care horror&lt;/a&gt;. (sunspark says)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dave Donelson&lt;/strong&gt; offers a glimmer of hope for an ugly war obscured by the news of Iraq and Afghanistan in &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/104354/553/144/670053"&gt;Baby Steps Toward Peace In Congo&lt;/a&gt;. (HansScholl)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;In &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/5/21135/7713/312/669901"&gt;Anti-Gay Rights Initiatives, Mormons and Mormon Church (LDS) Activism: An Historical Perspective&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;norm&lt;/strong&gt; analyzes all the salient points. (vcmvo2)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;Small business owner &lt;strong&gt;sharistuff&lt;/strong&gt; relates a tale of surviving from economic feast to famine in &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/144025/394"&gt;Darwinism for Your Business...Adapt or Die!&lt;/a&gt; (joyful)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WereBear&lt;/strong&gt; gives some keen practical advice on how to weather these hard times and the loss of a permanent (is there such a thing?) job in &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/95031/1879/189/670032"&gt;Temping: Your Path to Employment (with poll)&lt;/a&gt;. (HansScholl)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;Two looks at our deepening recession: &lt;strong&gt;rmonroe&lt;/strong&gt; shows us that it's &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/54913/0487"&gt;High Noon: Wall Street vs Main Street&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;jimstaro&lt;/strong&gt; offers a sobering news round-up in &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/85643/2792"&gt;"almost homeless"&lt;/a&gt;. (srkp23)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Aeon For Change 93&lt;/strong&gt; addresses a very important topic in &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/14320/3239/85/670120"&gt;Child Abuse: What Every Parent Needs to Know&lt;/a&gt;. (sunspark says)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deep Harm&lt;/strong&gt; keeps us up-to-date with this news round-up: &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/73319/1175"&gt;Melamine Crisis Update, Week of 12/6/08&lt;/a&gt;. (srkp23)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dem Beans&lt;/strong&gt; introduces &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/5/184432/132/365/669856"&gt;The smallest survivor&lt;/a&gt;, an adorable friend rescued from a bad situation. (mem from somerville) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;jotter&lt;/strong&gt; has &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/104124/661/145/670052"&gt;High Impact Diaries: December 5, 2008&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;carolita&lt;/strong&gt; has &lt;a href="http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/19731/7367/0/670197"&gt;Top Comments 12-6-08 -- Music, Music, Music Edition&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Enjoy and please promote your own favorite diaries in this open thread (even if you're the author! Here's where that's actually appreciated). And, of course, since it's an open thread, PLAY NICE, OK? 8^)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/ExXwUppVEMbeo9QDRV74uj_mxpM/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/ExXwUppVEMbeo9QDRV74uj_mxpM/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=wNk4s59i"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/VkpTfy0HeSE" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>Diary Rescue &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>open thread</category>
<category>diary rescue</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">670244</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 04:53:57 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/234840/061/986/670244</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>LA-04 Results Thread #2</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/eqBA8oUqc0w/670232</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RESULTS&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="http://www400.sos.louisiana.gov:8090/cgibin/?rqstyp=elcms2&amp;amp;rqsdta=120608"&gt;LA SoS&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href="http://hosted.ap.org/dynamic/files/elections/2008/by_state/LA_US_House_1206.html?SITE=LASHT&amp;amp;SECTION=POLITICS"&gt;Associated Press&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10:53PM&lt;/strong&gt;: Caddo has finished reporting and it's now 49-47 Carmouche. All the remaining votes are in Bossier Parish. If the current 58-36 margin for Fleming holds there, we might eke out a narrow win.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10:56PM&lt;/strong&gt;: My back-of-the-envelope suggests a virtual tie (Carmouche +100 votes) if the oustanding Bossier precincts look like those already in - in other words, far too close to actually predict anything.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, in LA-02, the Republican still holds a 54-42 lead. Craziness.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11:03PM&lt;/strong&gt;: A heartbreaker - the final Bossier precincts come in, giving Fleming a 44,497 to 44,141 win over Carmouche.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11:07PM&lt;/strong&gt;: 53-43 in LA-02. Perhaps tightening a bit.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;As for LA-04, the final margin was 0.38%, making this one of the closest races of 2008. I doubt a recount could change things. As for provisionals, there would have to be a lot outstanding and go heavily for Carmouche to make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11:12PM&lt;/strong&gt;: Pretty stunning - looks like the AP has called it for Cao. With 79% in, he has a 10% lead.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11:14PM&lt;/strong&gt;: LA-02 is a D+28 district according to the &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cook_Partisan_Voting_Index"&gt;Cook Partisan Voting Index&lt;/a&gt;. That means it's 28 points more Democratic than the nation as a whole (going off the 2004 presidential results - PVIs haven't been updated for 2008 yet). To give you a sense of how Dem this district is, there is not a single Republican district that is comparably red - UT-03 tops the list at R+26.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11:53PM&lt;/strong&gt;: In the end, Cao wins 50-47.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/sPFQSJ-SNafcZ_-rur7vCNGqwAc/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/sPFQSJ-SNafcZ_-rur7vCNGqwAc/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=cqE0CCBN"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/eqBA8oUqc0w" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>DavidNYC &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>LA-04</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">670232</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 03:54:28 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/225058/154/1006/670232</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>LA-04 Results Thread</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/_kb-dgg-AYE/670216</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www400.sos.louisiana.gov:8090/cgibin/?rqstyp=elcms2&amp;amp;rqsdta=120608"&gt;94% of precincts reporting&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;div class="indent"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paul J. Carmouche&lt;/strong&gt; (D) &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;49% &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;(41794) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John Fleming&lt;/strong&gt; (R) &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 47% &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;(39936) &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gerard Bowen&lt;/strong&gt; (I) &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 1% &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;"Catfish" Kelley&lt;/strong&gt; (I) &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 3% &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: Super tight so far; only 77 votes separating the leaders. Still too early to even try and forecast anything.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: Carmouche leads!...er, no, Fleming got it back.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: The back and forth continues, but with nearly 30% in, Carmouche has his biggest lead of the night.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: Fleming turf coming in, Carmouche now just 25 votes ahead. Still 55% of precincts to be counted.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: Fleming takes lead, Carmouche takes it back. Don't you DARE touch that dial.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: It may actually be almost possible that William Jefferson might lose in LA-02. I would bet heavily against it...but with 16% in, Jefferson is down 54-41.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: 83% in. Looks excellent for Carmouche.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Think about this: Dems may pick up an R+7 district, while a Republican just might capture a D+28 district. Jefferson is down 58-39 with 30% in.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update&lt;/strong&gt;: Carmouche is still well ahead, though his margin is under 2,000 votes. Fleming-friendly Bossier Parish isn't all in, so he could close substantially, but it looks like Carmouche's to lose at this point.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Jefferson/Cao numbers also starting to even out; with ovr 50% of precincts &amp;nbsp;reporting Cao is up 53-43. I still think Jefferson will win.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/b3FeMkikb80yeyknPiE90-ix3DE/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/b3FeMkikb80yeyknPiE90-ix3DE/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=OkslCMXV"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/_kb-dgg-AYE" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>brownsox &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>LA-04</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">670216</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 02:18:45 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/211425/147/1022/670216</feedburner:origLink></item>

<item>
<title>Misled Our Country Into War? (Laughter)</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/Bm37elwN3Gk/669394</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Looking back at the lies that the Bush administration peddled through the traditional media to sell the disastrous war in Iraq, one might assume that the media would finally stop being such spineless toadies and once again become actual journalists. Unfortunately, one would be &lt;a href="http://www.whitehouse.gov/news/releases/2008/12/20081204-1.html"&gt;wrong&lt;/a&gt;, because after eight long years of this psychodrama, both sides are still playing the same roles, having learned absolutely nothing.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt; Q: In these recent interviews, has the President ever expressed regret over attacking Iraq? And also, is Karl Rove in charge of promoting legacy?&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[CliffNotes version: no and no]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Q: What about the chief of British intelligence saying you were going to fix the facts around the policy?&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;MS. PERINO: I think that that's been debunked, and --&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Q It's never been debunked.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;MS. PERINO: Well, it's been debunked by me. (Laughter.)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Q Good for you.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;MS. PERINO: Yes, good for me.	(Laughter.)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Q And is the White House sponsoring these interviews with -- on legacy? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Translation: Oh, Dana, we &lt;a href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2005/05/12/AR2005051201857.html"&gt;know&lt;/a&gt; that this administration cooked the books to get us into war even though we've mostly ignored that story, but you're so funnny, we'll just &lt;a href="http://icasualties.org/oif/"&gt;laugh&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://icasualties.org/oif/IraqiDeaths.aspx"&gt;laugh&lt;/a&gt; with you before moving onto important questions about creating a legacy for George Bush.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/rf-B_4VI24hcMuJ3CIDFFLKXV0A/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/rf-B_4VI24hcMuJ3CIDFFLKXV0A/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=kkDPlfpq"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/Bm37elwN3Gk" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>BarbinMD &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>Dana Perino</category>
<category>White House press briefing</category>
<category>Iraq</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">669394</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 01:38:51 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/203848/835/803/669394</feedburner:origLink></item>


<item>
<title>Misled Our Country Into Wa? (Laugheuue</title>
<link>http://feeds.dailykos.com/~r/dailykos/index/~3/Bm37elwN3Gk/669394</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Looking back at the lies that the Bush administration peddled through the traditional media to sell the disastrous war in Iraq, one might assume that the media would finally stop being such spineless toadies and once again become actual journalists. Unfortunately, one would be &lt;a href="http://www.whitehouse.gov/news/releases/2008/12/20081204-1.html"&gt;wrong&lt;/a&gt;, because after eight long years of this psychodrama, both sides are still playing the same roles, having learned absolutely nothing.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt; Q: In these recent interviews, has the President ever expressed regret over attacking Iraq? And also, is Karl Rove in charge of promoting legacy?&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;[CliffNotes version: no and no]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Q: What about the chief of British intelligence saying you were going to fix the facts around the policy?&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;MS. PERINO: I think that that's been debunked, and --&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Q It's never been debunked.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;MS. PERINO: Well, it's been debunked by me. (Laughter.)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Q Good for you.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;MS. PERINO: Yes, good for me.	(Laughter.)&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Q And is the White House sponsoring these interviews with -- on legacy? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Translation: Oh, Dana, we &lt;a href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2005/05/12/AR2005051201857.html"&gt;know&lt;/a&gt; that this administration cooked the books to get us into war even though we've mostly ignored that story, but you're so funnny, we'll just &lt;a href="http://icasualties.org/oif/"&gt;laugh&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://icasualties.org/oif/IraqiDeaths.aspx"&gt;laugh&lt;/a&gt; with you before moving onto important questions about creating a legacy for George Bush.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/rf-B_4VI24hcMuJ3CIDFFLKXV0A/a"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedads.googleadservices.com/~a/rf-B_4VI24hcMuJ3CIDFFLKXV0A/i" border="0" ismap="true"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="feedflare"&gt;
&lt;a href="http://feeds.dailykos.com/~f/dailykos/index?a=kkDPlfpq"&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~f/dailykos/index?d=120" border="0"&gt;&lt;/img&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/dailykos/index/~4/Bm37elwN3Gk" height="1" width="1"/&gt;</description>
<author>BarbinMD &lt;rss@dailykos.com&gt;</author>
<category>Dana Perino</category>
<category>White House press briefing</category>
<category>Iraq</category>
<guid isPermaLink="false">669394</guid>
<pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2008 01:38:51 GMT</pubDate>
<feedburner:origLink>http://www.dailykos.com/storyonly/2008/12/6/203848/835/803/669394</feedburner:origLink></item>

<textInput>
<title>Search Daily Kos</title>
<description>Use the text box to search Daily Kos</description>
<name>string</name>
<link>http://www.dailykos.com/search/</link>
</textInput>

</channel>
</rss>
